nuaodisha.com 2014-06-25

# www.nuaodisha.com : PrivacyPolicy

|  |  |  |   
---|---|---  
| 

  * Send Free SMS
  * Odia Jokes
  * Dainik Rasiphala(Horoscope)
  * Odia Calendar - 2014
  * Odia Old and New MP3 Songs
  * Voter-Id Registration Steps
  * Odia Dhaga Dhamali
  * Odia e-Greeting Cards
  * FB Comments Funny Pics
  * Odisha Train Timings
  * Odisha Classified Ads
  * Odisha Exam Results
  * Know Your PF Balance Online
  * Apply for a PAN Card Online
  * Trace Mobile Number Location
  * Photos Of Ancient Odisha 
  * Lord Jagannath Culture
  * Odia Hanuman Chalisha
  * Ayurvedic Home Remedies
  * Odia Poetry and Short Stories
  * Odisha General Information
  * Tourist Places of Odisha
  * Government of Odisha
  * Pride of Odisha
  * Educational Institutions
  * Learn Odia @ Virtual e-School
  * How to Write Odia in Google
  * Health N Food Tips
  * NGO Corner
  * View Registered Members
  * Register As Member

|   
  |    |    
|  |   
  |  |    
  
| 

## Privacy Policy  
  
---  
  
  1. We collect personally identifiable information, when somebody registers in nuaodisha.com. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. The registered members of our website are automatically added to our mailing list. You as a subscriber of the mailing list have the option to opt out of these mailing list by clicking on the unsubscribe link in any of the newsletter sent to you. 

  2. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

  3. Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

  4. The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. 

  5. We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. Other than this, we have our own network of websites and portals. From time to time, we may send you the relevant information from these websites or portals also.

  6. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

  7. nuaodisha.com may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.

  8. If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact nuaodiha2011@gmail.com
